<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<!--?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.xsl"?-->
<plan plan-format="1.0" xmlns="http://www.eclipse.org/project/plan"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="VIATRA2">
	<release projectid="modeling.gmt.viatra2" version="0.1" />
	<introduction>
		<html:div>The main objective of the VIATRA2 (VIsual Automated model TRAnsformations) framework is to provide a general-purpose support for the entire life-cycle of engineering model transformations including the specification, design, execution, validation and maintenance of transformations within and between various modeling languages and domains.
		</html:div>
	</introduction>
	<release_deliverables>
		<html:p>
			Each release provides development tools and an execution engine VIATRA2 transformations.
		</html:p>
	</release_deliverables>
	<release_milestones>
		<milestone date="02/06/2008" milestone="3.0.0"></milestone>
		<milestone date="04/29/2010" milestone="3.1.0"></milestone>		
		<milestone date="04/11/2011" milestone="3.2.0"></milestone>	
		<milestone date="31/08/2012" milestone="3.3.0"><html:b>(planned)</html:b></milestone>
	</release_milestones>
	<target_environments>
		<html:div>
			VIATRA2 depends on the Platform and offers optional integration with EMF. VIATRA2 has been compiled using Java 1.6 and does not depend on any non-Java libraries.
		</html:div>
		<internationalization>
			<html:div>
			VIATRA2 does not currently provide support for internationalization.
			</html:div>
		</internationalization>
	</target_environments>
	<themes_and_priorities>
		<theme name="EMF Compatibility">
			<description>
				<html:div>
					We are working on making a native EMF version of VIATRA2 that will allow VIATRA2's scalable transformations to be executed directly on EMF models without the necessity for import/export.
				</html:div>
			</description>
		</theme>
		<theme name="Performance enhancements">
			<description>
				<html:div>
					We are working on enhancing the performance of VIATRA2 by optimizing the incremental pattern matching engine to enable users to usebig/complex industrial models.
				</html:div>
			</description>
		</theme>
		<theme name="Community building">
			<description>
				<html:div>
					VIATRA2 already has a substantial user community. We are constantly working on extending the VIATRA2 community by publishing examples and tutorials online on the VIATRA2 Eclipse.org wiki. 
				</html:div>
			</description>
		</theme>
		</themes_and_priorities>
	<appendix name="Legal Notices">
		<html:div>
			<ul>
				<li>
					Java is a trademark or a registered trademark of Sun Microsystems, Inc.
            </li>
				<li>
					All other products or company names are mentioned for identification purposes only,
					and may be trademarks or service marks of their respective owners.
            </li>
			</ul>
		</html:div>
	</appendix>
</plan>